How to Lose a Popularity Contest is a romance, comedy
film directed by Stephen S. Campanelli.
A rebellious student and a perfectionist overachiever form an unlikely alliance in their race
for student body president, discovering unexpected feelings along the way.
Ellie Pearse, played by Sara Waisglass.
Nate Reed, played by Chase Hudson.
Quinn, played by Lillian Doucet-Roche.
Rowan Cross, played by Graham Verchere.
Gloria Everdeen, played by Ecstasia Sanders.
Aja Fox, played by Kyra Leroux.
Graham Marc Verchere is a Canadian actor.
He is known for roles in Stargirl, Fargo, The Good Doctor and Summer of 84.
The film explores themes of high school,
overachiever, teenage romance, student council.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.